[Music]
it's um truly a privilege to receive
this award on behalf of the leadership
team at credential Singapore being one
of the best companies to work for um at
credential we speak about our purpose
every day which is to help people get
the most out of life and that's become a
mantra to each and every one of our
employees who turn up for work every day
to make life better not just for
themselves but our customers our
partners our Distributors and our fellow
colleagues and by a larger extension the
community so if anyone deserves this
award is every one of our 1,200
employees who are the unsung heroes who
have really strive through the pandemic
and come out with flying colors so I
salute you I salute you for your
resilience I salute you for your hard
work but more importantly I thank you
for choosing to be part of credential
Singapore and helping us live our
purpose to help people get the most out
of life every single day thank you so
much